# Morteza Shoushtari

Graduate Research Assistant shoushtari.morteza@live.com Number: +1 (385) 450-9843

Linkedin profile

#### Summary

I am a Ph.D. student in the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE), Brigham Young University. Currently, I am working on physical layer security, and SECC coding. I received an M.S. degree in Information Technology from Shiraz University, Iran, in 2013. I have 6 years of work experience as an IT administrator and network engineer.

### RESEARCH Interests

- Computer Networks
- Cloud Computing
- Physical Layer Security
- Security/Error-Correction Coding

#### EDUCATION

Ph.D., Computer Engineering

Dissertation topic: Secrecy in Caching Channels **Brigham Young University**, Utah, USA

• Years: 2019 - 2023 (expected)

• GPA: 3.74/4

M.Sc., Information Technology (IT) Shiraz University, Shiraz, IRAN

Years: 2011 - 2013GPA: 3.69/4

B.Sc., Computer Engineering

Sadjad University of Technology, Mashhad, IRAN

Years: 2006 - 2010GPA: 3.47/4

#### Publication

• Willie Harrison and Morteza Shoushtari, "On Caching with Finite Blocklength Coding for Secrecy over the Binary Erasure Wiretap Channel" in Proceedings of IEEE Global Communications Conference (GLOBECOM), (Taipei, Taiwan), Dec. 2020.

### Work Experiences

# Brigham Young University, UTAH, USA

Jan 2019 - present

Graduate Research Assistant

• RA with the emphasize on physical layer security and coded-caching

# IT Dep. HUAWEI Company, Tehran, Iran

Aug 2016 - Aug 2017

#### IT Administrator

- Maintained communication networks, monitor network performance, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24\*7 level one support over 850 clients
- Installed and configured network devices, including routers, switches, wireless AP's, camera's, and video conferences
- Strong contribution in Huawei IT department in Middle-East region

## IT Dep. JYAN Company, Tehran, Iran

Jan 2016 - Aug 2016

#### **Network Engineer**

- Maintained communication networks, monitor network performance, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24\*7 level one support over 180 clients
- Installed and configured network devices, including routers, switches, wireless AP's, camera's, and video conferences

## IT Dep. Persia Cloud Company, Tehran, Iran **Network Engineer**

Jun 2015 - Jan 2016

- Installed and configured 2X and IIRAS cloud platforms (IIAS, PAAS)
- Installed and configured Microsoft Servers (CRM, SharePoint, Lync)

## IT Dep. LOTUS Company, Tehran, Iran Website Developer

Nov 2013 - Jun 2015

- Programmed and maintained company's website (lotuslaptop.com)

### IT Dep. KARMA Engineering Company, Iran Technical Support

Nov 2011 - Nov 2013

- Maintained communication networks, and resolved any technical issues
- Provided 24\*7 level one support over 50 clients
- Installed and configured technical software

#### HONORS

- Ranked 6th among graduate students studying IT at Shiraz University with an overall GPA of 3.7/4 (Out of 35)
- Monthly star engineer in JYANE Company-2016
- Outstanding IT engineer in Huawei Technologies Company -2017

### CERTIFICATES AND SKILLS

- IT Certificates:
  - o CompTIA A+
  - o CompTIA Network+
  - o CCNA (Cisco Certified Network Associate)
  - o MCITP (Microsoft Certified IT Professional)
  - o HCNA (Huawei Certified Network Associate)
- Skills in computer networks:
  - o Install and configure network devices (Switch, routers, ...)
  - o Install and configure virtual networks with VMware ESX, VCenter
  - o Knowledge in Cloud Computing Architecture such as AWS, 2x (Parallels)
  - o Network troubleshooting
- Technical knowledge:
  - o Programming Language: C/C++/Python/Matlab/Web Programming
  - o Operating Systems: Microsoft Windows Client-Server/Linux
  - o Software development methodology: Scrum/RUP

#### LANGUAGE SKILLS

Persian - Native

English - Fluent

Spanish - Basic